accessexcellence.org 2018-09-02

# Search Access Excellence

## Access Excellence Privacy Policy

Access Excellence at the National Health Museum respects the privacy of our online visitors. We are committed to protecting your privacy and security while you visit our web site. This privacy policy will let you how we protect your personal information. Please read it carefully. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please let us know by sending an email to [[Contact us by email] ](https://web.archive.org/web/20180902131558id_/http%3A//www.accessexcellence.org/captcha/email.cgi.html).

**Information Collected and Stored Automatically**

When you visit Access Excellence (www.accessexcellence.org) and browse through the web site or download information, we will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally.

**What types of information do we collect when you visit our web site?**

  * the pages you visit 

  * the date and time you access our site

  * the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are coming from an America Online account) 

  * the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site 

  * your operating system and browser 

**Why do we collect this type of information?  
**

  * to measure the number of visitors to the different sections and activities found on our site 

  * to help us make our site more useful   

**Personal Information**   

Access Excellence will not sell, trade, or give out e-mail addresses to companies or other organizations. We will not intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you without your permission. We may request personal identification information from you in connection with your participation in contests, games, surveys, submissions, chat and bulletin boards. However, we will only collect this personal information from you voluntarily.

Any personal information voluntarily provided to us may be used in connection with the activities already mentioned. For instance, if you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your name and email address to write a response. We may also keep your comments or questions for future reference.
